# **Gregory Strom**

# Full Stack Web Developer

Web developer redeploying exceptional communication and analytic skills honed as a University-level teacher of philosophy and logic into a programming career. Extensive international experience collaborating with students and colleagues to solve conceptual problems and find ways to make exciting ideas work.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Administrative Secretary, September 2019 – present | Pittsburgh University of Pittsburgh, Department of Physics & Astronomy

- Maintained and updated Laboratory of Ultrafast Dynamics website
- Built and maintained the page for the ongoing International Ultrafast Knowledge Coffee House lecture series

**Assistant Teacher**, September 2020 – present | **New York** Math-M-Addicts

- Taught weekly online course introducing advanced math concepts to children ages 10-12
- Prepared and conducted parent/teacher conferences

**Visiting Lecturer/Instructor**, August 2013 – May 2021 | **Pittsburgh** University of Pittsburgh, Department of Philosophy

- Reinstated and organized annual philosophy conference with contributors from multiple institutions
- Created syllabuses and delivered lectures for 27 undergraduate philosophy courses
- Designed and directed 17 adult education courses for the Osher Lifelong Learning Institute
- Supervised and evaluated teams of teaching assistants

**Special Faculty**, August 2019 – December 2020 | **Pittsburgh** Carnegie Mellon University, Department of Philosophy

 Created syllabuses and delivered lectures for 4 undergraduate philosophy courses

Postdoctoral Fellow, July 2011 – July 2013 | Sydney, Australia University of Sydney, Centre for Time

- Coordinated weekly international guest speaker program
- Instructed graduate level courses in philosophy and supervised graduate level dissertation project

**Website Manager**, January 2011 – August 2011 | **Pittsburgh** University of Pittsburgh, Department of Philosophy

- Maintained and updated faculty supervisor's academic website
- Proofread and indexed faculty supervisor's book-length manuscript for publication

gbstrom@gmail.com +1-412-759-4591 Pittsburgh, PA, USA github.com/gbstrom linkedin.com/in/gbstrom gbstrom.github.io/portfolio/

## **SKILLS**

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- React Native
- Angular
- Git
- Responsive Design
  - jQuery
- Test Driven Development
- Configuring Heroku
- AWS
- MongoDB

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Certificate in Full Stack Web Development**

CareerFoundry - online May 2021 – March 2022

#### PhD in Philosophy

University of Pittsburgh August 2003 – August 2011

### **BA in Philosophy**

University of Chicago September 1998 – June 2002

#### RESEARCH

'Deviant Causal Chains, Knowledge of Reasons, and Akrasia'

Published in Topoi, April 2014

'Multitasking, Consequentialism and Practical Imagination'

PhD Thesis, University of Pittsburgh, 2011